Hey Monica this is a feedback video for
your final but it's gonna be an easy
one for me to record because you did
great As far as I could tell you
didn't skip any questions and there was nowhere
where I felt that you left something important
out So nice job on that Um rather
than go through your exam and just say
good job over and over and over I
picked a couple of places where you said
something interesting and I'll just comment on it
in the spirit of discussion but not in
the spirit of constructive criticism You honestly did
excellently Um I felt that you had a
really insightful discussion about the the dev cycle
um so Uh either you've been through it
enough times yourself or you you seem to
understand it pretty well so kudos on that
Um I believe the next thing I wanted
to mention was about chat GPT In the
question about web apps if I recall correctly
Uh I might have passed it up or
maybe it's later on um So I'll just
mention this part I This made me realize
that my metaphor about CSS being the skin
is a little bit grotesque and it's actually
a much nicer way to explain it to
say that CSS is like the person's clothes
their style like literally their style Um it
makes a lot more sense I think people
will remember it better so um I'm gonna
start changing the way I explain CSS Uh
this is uh this is a nice a
nicer way of saying it than I have
been saying it in the past Um Oh
I enjoyed your arc from uh the operating
system being your least favorite question to it
being actually not your least favorite and I
agree operating system does a lot of stuff
and it's a complicated piece of software um
but it it can be fun to start
Peeling back those layers of complexity Ah 6
degrees of separation Um you are right to
be convinced that this is not a fact
and not proven That that is true It
is not proven It may be a fact
who knows but we don't know because we
can't exhaustively test every pair of people on
the planet It's too many Uh but We
can explore 6 degrees of separation from a
mathematical perspective We can prove mathematically certain things
about networks that have the 6 degrees of
separation property or we can show that networks
that have some other property automatically must have
the 6 degrees of separation property That's in
the mathematical space Those mathematical proofs exist and
they are pretty fascinating but there's no empirical
scientific proof that shows that our world as
it is today With its particular social network
has these properties that have been explored in
the mathematical space So um really cool video
that I enjoyed about this topic which I'll
just recommend to you I may have already
done it I might have mentioned it in
class um but this is a this is
a fun 30 minutes Something strange happens when
you trace how connected we are by Veritasium
So recommend looking into that if you want
to uh do some more research I think
that might have been it I know at
the very end There was maybe some concern
because there were 46 questions but you did
it right you set it to 70 and
46 is the magic number this quarter for
the final so If you went through 2
hours of an exam and then ended it
uh worried that you did it wrong Sorry
that this is coming 3 weeks late but
you did it right and it was a
great exam and I'll see you next time